# Jordi Jaspers

# Software Engineer

Master graduate in Electronic & Software engineering, combined with 5+ years of professional experience in the IT industry and a passion for developing and discovering new technologies. Always striving to resolve issues and create new features as efficient as possible. Supporting code with enough test-driven design to ensure high quality solutions. Being involved the complete Software Development Life Cycle, including analysis, design, development, testing, implementation, support, and maintenance of enterprise-level web applications mainly using Java/Java EE.

### Contact

#### **Address**

Lanaken, Limburg 3620

#### **Phone**

(+32) 47145 64 35

#### E-mail

jordijaspers@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/jordi-jaspers

#### Github

github.com/Jordi-Jaspers

#### CodeWars

<u>codewars.com/users/Jordi-</u>
Jaspers

### Languages

Dutch	•••• Excellent
English	•••• Excellent
French	•••OC Good
German	••OOC Average

# **Professional Experience**

### 2021-02 Medior Software Engineer

Current Ilionx, Maastricht, Netherlands

- Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.
- Building enterprise grade software solutions using Java frameworks and test-driven design.
- Gathered and defined customer requirements to develop clear specifications for project plans.
- Reviewing code bases for bugs and weaknesses using approved troubleshooting methods, to prevents systems being exploited.

### 2013-04 Electrician

2014-08 Electro Geenard, Gellik, Belgium

- Planned layout and installation of electrical wiring, equipment and fixtures based on specifications and applicable code.
- Developed insight and skill about electrical circuits.

### **Certifications**

Oracle	Oracle certified SQL Developer
Coursera	Oracle Database Design and Management
Coursera	Advanced Micronaut & Spring development
Coursera	Machine Learning Basics
VCA	Safety on the Work floor
Hapkido	Official Hapkido Trainer - 3rd Grade Black Belt

# **Coding Languages**

Java CSS
Golang HTML
Python SQL
Kotlin Bash
Groovy Haskell
Javascript VHDL
Typescript C++

# **Technologies**

Liquibase	Jira
Git	Postman
Docker	Scriptrunner
Spring	Linux
Micronaut	Intellij
Grail	TailwindCSS

# **Education**

2020-07

2020 07	masici s mesis income a commune ingineering
2021-02	Hanyang University - Ansan, Seoul, Korea
Subject:	Inventing a framework for anomaly detection in the radio spectrum.
2019-09 2021-01	Master of Science: Electronic & Software Engineering  UHasselt   KULeuven – Diepenbeek
Courses:	OOP in Java, Compilers, Algorithms, Operating Systems, Data Structures, Docker, Advanced Mathematics, VHDL & FPGA programming.
2015-09	Bachelor of Science: Electronic & Software Engineering
2019-01	UHasselt   KULeuven – Diepenbeek
Courses:	Machine Learning 101, Signals & systems, Databases & structures, Digital
	systems, Functional Programming in Haskell, Software Design in C++, Unix
	Operating systems and Linux Distros, Chip-design, Telecomunication.

Master's Thesis Electronic & Software Engineering

# **Volunteering Experience**

Martial Arts Instructor, Sin Moo Hapkido | Rekem, Limburg Responsibilities:

- 3rd grade black belt instructor
- Imparted key etiquette points, discipline, and respect.
- Taught both core principles and fighting techniques to students of all levels.
- Helped students prevent injuries and rendered calm and professional aid in case of accidents.

Projects total: 9

Mitre-Upgrade Vodafone-Ziggo

### Java developer:

- Upgraded a custom SSO implementation and ensured its older capabilities.
- Removed security risks found during the upgrade.
- Cleaned-up / Refactored code during the upgrade for increased readability & maintenance.
- Bumping to Java 17 with new Gradle versions to keep software on the latest versions.

### DevOps:

- Redesigned Liquibase environment to ensure a seamless migration to PRD.
- Added security measurements and checks in the CI/CD.
- Altered Jenkins so, the Liquibase redesign works on every environment (DEV, TST, ACC).

### App-Billing (Formula 1)

Vodafone-Ziggo & Viaplay

### Full-Stack:

- Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.
- Design a flow to produce tokens which enables customers to authorize their payment to other streaming services (Netflix, Viaplay, ...)
- Integrated a Redis caching system to temporarily save JWT tokens in a secure way.
- Setup a Microservice from scratch without any issues.
- Supporting other parties to pursue seamless SIT and UAT transition.
- Configuring properties needed for the environment (SIT, UAT, PRD)
- Created & altered the design to cohere with the microservices of multiple squads of different companies.
- Made design decisions based on the specifications of the client.

### **Multi-factor Authentication**

Vodafone-Ziggo

### Java developer:

- Altering the usual authentication flows of our own custom SSO implementation.
- Using Spring security to add authentication filters.
- Integrating 3rd party tools to fetch IP & user agent data.
- Adding 2FA with a "Remember me" function based on location and user data.

### Test Engineer:

- Creating Integration test and unit test to handle all possible cases.
- Using Cypress to test end-to-end cases with other parties.

**StateHistory** Vodafone-Ziggo

### Java developer:

- Maintaining the main monitoring tool an enterprise with a user base of 2 million or 9.7 million services.
- Optimizing advanced database queries to gain performance.